

NODIRBEK ULASHEV

JavaScript Engineer

Full-stack Web Developer

SUMMARY

As a JavaScript developer with background in developing and managing web applications, I am passionate about staying up to date with the latest technologies and continuing to grow in my career. With my skills and experience, I am confident in my abilities to deliver software solutions that meet the needs of businesses and end-users alike.

SKILLS

- · HTML5 & CSS3
- JavaScript (ES5 ESNext)
- · ReactJs & NextJs & Redux
- · Shopify App & Liquid Development
- TypeScript
- OpenAl
- · NestJs & ExpressJs
- · Webpack & Vite
- · MongoDB & Mongoose

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH C1, Advanced

RUSSIAN B2, Upper-Intermediate

UZBEK Native

CONTACT

+998

nodirbekulashev01@gmail.com

Tashkent, Shaykhantakhur, 100020 Uzbekistan

LINKS



www.min1one.me



www.linkedin.com/in/n-ulashev-min1one



t.me/ulashevn



github.com/MiN10ne

medium.com/@nodirbekulashev01

EXPERIENCE

JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER July 2021 - Current

LlamaCommerce, Remote, New York 10013 USA www.llamacommerce.io

- · Developing and maintaining Shopify based online stores.
- · Developing and deploying Al-powered solutions.
- Assisting newcomer developers in getting started with company tech-stack.
- · Developing Shopify applications and extensions (client-side, post-purchase, functions API, checkout UI).
- Developing custom middlewares using Storefont and Admin APIs.
- · Third-party service integrations.
- · Creating responsive UIs modular components.
- · Developing and maintaining headless applications.
- · Creating project workflows, scripts and setting up CI/CD.
- · Analyzing and optimizing product performance, structure and design.
- · Estimating and setting right deadlines.

Contributed projects:

- · www.bugatchi.com
- · www.wildone.com
- www.b2b.kassatex.com
- Upsell and Cross Sell apps.shopify.com/upsell-prod
- Manual Related Products apps.shopify.com/related-products-app
- · Bundle with Discount apps.shopify.com/discount-guru

JAVASCRIPT INTERN July 2021 - Aug 2021

EPAM Systems, Remote, Tashkent Uzbekistan www.epam.com

- · Took part in teamwork.
- · Learnt basics of NestJs and practiced git commands and workflows.
- · Was assigned to complete a demo project with required technologies that have to be learnt in the process of development.

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER Dec 2020 - June 2021

Self-employed, Tashkent Uzbekistan

- Laying out front-end of online stores, landing pages and web applications
- · Developing MVPs.
- · Understaning needs & proposing project plans and appropriate tech solutions.

Contributed projects:

- www.softit .uz
- jobfront.inminternational.uz prisunion.uz
- www.uzbtrip.com 180Gradus
- · itic.uz

EDUCATION

Aug 2019 - May 2023

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE - MANAGEMENT INFORMATION SYSTEMS

Webster University, Tashkent Uzbekistan, 3.27 GPA

Focus on Project Management, System Design, Basic Programming, Basic Financial and Managerial Accounting